<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<about>Boxtoppers began the day I ran out of wrapping paper. Needing to wrap a present in a hurry, I searched around the house and found one sheet of white tissue paper and piece of twine. Earlier that week I had made turquoise beads for a bracelet, and decided that I would tie a bead to the middle of the present. It looked so simple and elegant that soon I began tying these delicate beads on all my gifts. Shortly after beads came miniatures - tiny character cars, sock monkeys, pumpkins, dinosaurs, ballerina bunnies, party-pooper penguins and more. These adorable little creatures sit on top of boxes, adding life and character to presents.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br&gt;
 
On a personal note, I have always been into making things out of clay, but I never thought I would ever try to sell any of it. It was more of a hobby. The reason  I started Boxtoppers and chose to sell the things I was making was to help my cousin, Kathryn Moreland. Kathryn is four and a half years old, and loves music, water, laughing, playing with her older brother, looking through books, chocolate cake, and animals.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br&gt;  

Kathryn also has autism. This neurological disorder affects the functioning of the brain, causing problems with communication, behavior, sensory input and learning.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br&gt;

Her parents have done many things to help their daughter, but they want to be able to help her more and give her the opportunity to live a better life. After much research, my aunt and uncle decided that an Autism Service Dog would benefit Kathryn in ways that nothing else could compare.  A service dog can improve upon several issues that arise when raising a child with Autism, including: Improve Safety, Promote Social Skills, Give a "Meltdown" Focal Point, and Provide Consistency.
&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br&gt;
All Purpose Canines Inc. is an agency dedicated to "making a difference". Their mission statement matches our hopes: To provide individuals with special needs a properly trained service dog to help improve their quality of life, enhance their independence and reach their fullest potential.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br&gt;

The cost of training and delivering a dog is over $14,000.00.  This is why I started Boxtoppers.   
&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br&gt;
I believe that when people receive a gift with one of these critters sitting on top, they will feel good knowing that they are helping a little girl live a better life.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br&gt;

I hope that during this busy holiday season you will take a moment and pick up a few of these delightful Boxtoppers.   &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br&gt;

Thank you, from all of us.
 &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br&gt;
--malena

</about>