<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<dansbio>









&lt;b&gt;Daniel Paul Johns&lt;/b&gt; is an Australian vocalist, composer and guitarist, best known for his work in the successful rock band Silverchair. Growing up in Newcastle, New South Wales, Australia, he formed Silverchair at the age of 14. Johns has found it somewhat difficult to cope with the fame brought on, at one stage suffering from anorexia nervosa and depression. The band's career began when they were just 14 years old, and signed to Murmur Records in 1994, after their demo "Tomorrow" won a competition by the SBS TV programme Nomad, and was then picked up by radio network Triple J. Their first album release was Frogstomp, in 1995. 

&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

By 2002, Johns appeared to have recovered from his internal trauma and was ready for the release of what he regarded as his band's masterpiece, Diorama. However, just as the album was due for release Johns was struck down by a rare case of reactive arthritis and spent most of 2002 unable to perform. It was feared that he may not be able to perform for years, and perhaps would never play again. Still unable to play for extended periods, he performed again in October 2002 at the ARIA awards ceremony. The guitar line of "The Greatest View" had to be changed so Johns' hands would not lock up. His recovery proceeded apace, allowing Silverchair to perform an extended Australian, European and North American concert tour. 

&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

Johns announced his engagement to long-time girlfriend, actress, singer and model Natalie Imbruglia in late 2002, and they married on New Year's Eve 2003. 

&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

Johns has also done the side projects The Dissociatives as well as "I Can't Believe It's Not Rock" with dance musician Paul Mac. Some people have made the mistake of accidentally assuming that these two projects are the same, but they are in fact totally different in style and sound. In late 2005 Daniel Johns and the boys of Silverchair joined up again and admonished rumors of splitting by announcing the production of a new album. The new album, which is untitled as of yet, is set to be released in 2007, complete with a tour. 











</dansbio>