<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<dansbio>









Born under the name, &lt;b&gt;Paul McDermott&lt;/b&gt; on September 16th, is a musician, producer and remixer from Sydney, Australia (don't confuse with the UK Techno DJ and producer Paul Mac alias Paul Souter). McDermott formed the bands Smash Mac Mac, Itchee And Scratchee aka Boo Boo And Mace, The Lab and The Dissociatives as well as releasing records under his own name. He has also played with Severed Heads and Silverchair. He also worked as musical director on the Australian TV show Good News Week. Mac co-wrote and produced the single "Shut Up And Kiss Me" for the other McDermott and Fiona Horne. A Paul is a classically trained graduate of Sydney's Conservatorium, he has been a leading light in local electronica since forming the Lab in the late 1980's. In the 1990's his work with Itchee and Scratchee won him club renown and even some tabloid notoriety when, in an acceptance speech at the 1995 ARIA Awards, he gushingly thanked the ecstasy dealers of Australia. 
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Baz Luhrman tapped him for work on his hit album "Something For Everybody" in 1997 but it was Paul's hard hitting remixes later that year for the likes of silverchair, Grinspoon, and INXS that first brought him broader attention. In 1998 he added some sonic enhancements to silverchair's landmark album "Neon Ballroom". Soundtrack work for films such as "Head On" and "Sample People" followed as did a stint as a musical director on TV. Most recently he collaborated with silverchair frontman Daniel Johns to create the innovative online EP "I Can't Believe It's Not Rock". 
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Throughout all these different high profile activities Paul continued to help create music for the dance cognoscenti with acts like, Natalie Imbruglia Kiva, and collaborating on the international club smash "The History Of Disco Part 2". At one point during all of this he was involved in so many different projects that he was signed to five different record companies at once and that was just in Australia! Eventually the idea evolved for one cohesive album which would bring together all the disparate elements of Paul's work - irresistible dance tracks, moody chill out numbers, menacing big beats and intricate instrumental soundscapes. The project quickly took on a life of its own as, for almost two years, a series of visitors went up to the Blue Mountains ( former name of Paul's studio ) for some intimate music making. Hard times hit Paul between losing recordings and equipment from a a fire too the loss of his father and god-daughter. As driven as Paul is, it didn't stop him to do what he loves, create music. During this session he had recorded once again with Daniel Johns to release The Dissociatives self titled album.(2003-04). Inbetween this project Paul had written music and recorded tracks the same old way, in his own studio..new studio that is..The new studio he named Panic Room. The story goes; Paul and a few mates got together rebuildt another studio. This studio would be called, Panic Room. 'Panic Room' Paul's latest CD was released in 2005. Paul had also collaborated with Nick Littlemore (Pnau),Abby Dobson (Decoder Ring) Julian Hamilton (the Presets), Poxy Music, Itchee And Scratchee aka Boo Boo & Mace ( Andy Rantzen & Paul Mac), and other local muscians high and low from Australia to create 'Panic Room' ! Paul has just released his new single 'Love Declaration' featuring a cool re-mix from Mr Timothy! He has also taken the stage with silverchair to fill in on keyboards. And is co-producing silverchair's new album. To top off Mac's good luck streak he also was voted best Dance/DJ in Rolling Stone mag 2006 April issue! And is nominated for "Most Performed Dance Work" at the APRA's! 

&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="http://www.paulmac.com.au/" target ="blank"&gt;
Visit Paul's official website!&lt;/a&gt;


</dansbio>